[
  {
    "prompt": "When Thomas, Jessica, and Victoria met at the store, Victoria gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Thomas",
    "B": "Jessica",
    "C": "Victoria",
    "correct": "Jessica",
    "io_name": "Jessica",
    "s_name": "Thomas",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Clark, Kyle, and Alex met at the store, Alex gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Clark",
    "B": "Kyle",
    "C": "Alex",
    "correct": "Kyle",
    "io_name": "Kyle",
    "s_name": "Clark",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Frank, Thomas, and Victoria met at the store, Victoria gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Frank",
    "B": "Thomas",
    "C": "Victoria",
    "correct": "Thomas",
    "io_name": "Thomas",
    "s_name": "Frank",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When George, Kate, and Elizabeth met at the store, Elizabeth gave a bottle to",
    "A": "George",
    "B": "Kate",
    "C": "Elizabeth",
    "correct": "Kate",
    "io_name": "Kate",
    "s_name": "George",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When David, George, and Thomas met at the store, Thomas gave a bottle to",
    "A": "David",
    "B": "George",
    "C": "Thomas",
    "correct": "George",
    "io_name": "George",
    "s_name": "David",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When David, Kate, and Alex met at the store, Alex gave a bottle to",
    "A": "David",
    "B": "Kate",
    "C": "Alex",
    "correct": "Kate",
    "io_name": "Kate",
    "s_name": "David",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When George, Alan, and Elizabeth met at the store, Elizabeth gave a bottle to",
    "A": "George",
    "B": "Alan",
    "C": "Elizabeth",
    "correct": "Alan",
    "io_name": "Alan",
    "s_name": "George",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Kyle, Paul, and Elizabeth met at the store, Elizabeth gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Kyle",
    "B": "Paul",
    "C": "Elizabeth",
    "correct": "Paul",
    "io_name": "Paul",
    "s_name": "Kyle",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Madison, David, and Paul met at the store, Paul gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Madison",
    "B": "David",
    "C": "Paul",
    "correct": "David",
    "io_name": "David",
    "s_name": "Madison",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Thomas, Elizabeth, and Alan met at the store, Alan gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Thomas",
    "B": "Elizabeth",
    "C": "Alan",
    "correct": "Elizabeth",
    "io_name": "Elizabeth",
    "s_name": "Thomas",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Frank, Brian, and Kyle met at the store, Kyle gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Frank",
    "B": "Brian",
    "C": "Kyle",
    "correct": "Brian",
    "io_name": "Brian",
    "s_name": "Frank",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Alex, Anna, and Brandon met at the store, Brandon gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Alex",
    "B": "Anna",
    "C": "Brandon",
    "correct": "Anna",
    "io_name": "Anna",
    "s_name": "Alex",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Aaron, Alan, and Elizabeth met at the store, Elizabeth gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Aaron",
    "B": "Alan",
    "C": "Elizabeth",
    "correct": "Alan",
    "io_name": "Alan",
    "s_name": "Aaron",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Brandon, Kate, and William met at the store, William gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Brandon",
    "B": "Kate",
    "C": "William",
    "correct": "Kate",
    "io_name": "Kate",
    "s_name": "Brandon",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When George, Aaron, and Anna met at the store, Anna gave a bottle to",
    "A": "George",
    "B": "Aaron",
    "C": "Anna",
    "correct": "Aaron",
    "io_name": "Aaron",
    "s_name": "George",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When David, Kyle, and Jessica met at the store, Jessica gave a bottle to",
    "A": "David",
    "B": "Kyle",
    "C": "Jessica",
    "correct": "Kyle",
    "io_name": "Kyle",
    "s_name": "David",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When William, Paul, and Jessica met at the store, Jessica gave a bottle to",
    "A": "William",
    "B": "Paul",
    "C": "Jessica",
    "correct": "Paul",
    "io_name": "Paul",
    "s_name": "William",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Madison, Alex, and Kyle met at the store, Kyle gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Madison",
    "B": "Alex",
    "C": "Kyle",
    "correct": "Alex",
    "io_name": "Alex",
    "s_name": "Madison",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Jessica, Victoria, and Thomas met at the store, Thomas gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Jessica",
    "B": "Victoria",
    "C": "Thomas",
    "correct": "Victoria",
    "io_name": "Victoria",
    "s_name": "Jessica",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When William, Frank, and Alex met at the store, Alex gave a bottle to",
    "A": "William",
    "B": "Frank",
    "C": "Alex",
    "correct": "Frank",
    "io_name": "Frank",
    "s_name": "William",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Brian, Alan, and Aaron met at the store, Aaron gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Brian",
    "B": "Alan",
    "C": "Aaron",
    "correct": "Alan",
    "io_name": "Alan",
    "s_name": "Brian",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Brandon, Jessica, and George met at the store, George gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Brandon",
    "B": "Jessica",
    "C": "George",
    "correct": "Jessica",
    "io_name": "Jessica",
    "s_name": "Brandon",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Paul, Thomas, and Alex met at the store, Alex gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Paul",
    "B": "Thomas",
    "C": "Alex",
    "correct": "Thomas",
    "io_name": "Thomas",
    "s_name": "Paul",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Brian, Aaron, and Elizabeth met at the store, Elizabeth gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Brian",
    "B": "Aaron",
    "C": "Elizabeth",
    "correct": "Aaron",
    "io_name": "Aaron",
    "s_name": "Brian",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Sarah, Alan, and Kyle met at the store, Kyle gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Sarah",
    "B": "Alan",
    "C": "Kyle",
    "correct": "Alan",
    "io_name": "Alan",
    "s_name": "Sarah",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Alex, Kyle, and Frank met at the store, Frank gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Alex",
    "B": "Kyle",
    "C": "Frank",
    "correct": "Kyle",
    "io_name": "Kyle",
    "s_name": "Alex",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Kyle, Elizabeth, and David met at the store, David gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Kyle",
    "B": "Elizabeth",
    "C": "David",
    "correct": "Elizabeth",
    "io_name": "Elizabeth",
    "s_name": "Kyle",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Brian, Clark, and Victoria met at the store, Victoria gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Brian",
    "B": "Clark",
    "C": "Victoria",
    "correct": "Clark",
    "io_name": "Clark",
    "s_name": "Brian",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Thomas, Paul, and Frank met at the store, Frank gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Thomas",
    "B": "Paul",
    "C": "Frank",
    "correct": "Paul",
    "io_name": "Paul",
    "s_name": "Thomas",
    "template": "ABC"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "When Frank, Madison, and William met at the store, William gave a bottle to",
    "A": "Frank",
    "B": "Madison",
    "C": "William",
    "correct": "Madison",
    "io_name": "Madison",
    "s_name": "Frank",
    "template": "ABC"
  }
]